<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DNAP Histrion</string>
    <string name="title_location_permission">Requesting for Location Info</string>
    <string name="text_location_permission">It is recommended that you allow this app to be able to save the active location, as a mechanism to help you tell where you data was last accessed should you ever request for it or need this.</string>
    <string name="DEFAULT_CHANNEL_REPO_QUERY_PREFIX">https://chwezi.tech/api/channel/personas/?c=%s&amp;_t=%o</string>
    <string name="getting_started_historion_message">
        This section of the app contains any personas sent to your device from the official theatre.
        Right now, it is blank, because none have been fetched or sent yet.
        \n\n
        FIRST, ensure you have an active Internet connection, and that your phone has data - this is required to fetch the dynamic personas at least once - the first time.
        \n\n
        If you believe there should have been some persona shown here, but which isn\'t, possibly go into the "Manage Personas" section (see menu), click the "REFRESH" menu action, and then activate
        one of the personas listed. Otherwise, it might be that your app isn\'t pointing to the correct Persona Channel.
        \n\nIf the above is okay, and yet you still see no personas after using the "Manage Personas" menu, then just try to restart this app - it\'s possible they were fetched, but none was loaded yet.
        \n\n
        If you totally fail to get a persona showing here, and yet your developers indicate one was published to your channel, report this problem to them soon as possible.
    </string>
    <string name="title_cant_save_act">CAN\'T SAVE Data!</string>
    <string name="invalid_persona_uuid">The Persona this form is based on, has no UUID or setting the UUID has failed. Contact the designers of this current persona for help.</string>
    <string name="action_manage_personas_short">Manage</string>
    <string name="action_manage_personas">Manage Personas</string>
    <string name="action_fetch_personas">Fetch Personas</string>
    <string name="action_fetch_personas_short">Refresh</string>
    <string name="title_activity_manage_persona">All Personas</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
